GUILHERME MORONE ARAUJO

Software Engineer

- @ guimorone@gmail.com
- https://guimorone.github.io

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/guimorone
- Recife, Pernambuco, Brazil



EDUCATION

Bachelor, Computer Engineering

Federal University of Pernambuco

· Expect to graduate by August 2024.

GPA (CR)

9.07 / 10.0

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Neurotech

A https://www.neurotech.com.br

Full-time (Hybrid)

- In general, using skills in backend development (FastAPI), data engineering, Terraform, Git, Airflow and cloud computing (AWS).
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to achieve project goals.
- Ensure high-quality, scalable application development.
- Using Amazon Web Services such as Lambda, DynamoDB, EC2, Athena, S3 and more.

Software Engineer

https://www.jalan.com.br

Full-time (Remote)

Worked as a Full Stack developer using Vue.js and Quasar along with Python and Lambda Functions (AWS).

Mobile Engineer

= 03/2024 - 03/2024

Recife, Pernambuco, Brazil

Freelancer (Remote)

Worked as a Mobile Engineer in a Freelancer project (aca.so mobile app) using React Native.

Full Stack Developer

Cheque Fácil

m 09/2023 - 12/2023

Recife, Pernambuco, Brazil

Freelancer (Remote)

- Website made with 3 more colleagues to an external customer.
- The main purpose is to identify bank check fields easily, so you do not have to type manually.
- The bank check OCR is based on our customer's API, we did not implement it, just the website.
- It also offers API Integration, history download and other features.
- Developed using React, TypeScript, TailwindCSS and Django (Python).

Mobile Engineer

InSpace

m 08/2022 - 10/2022

Recife, Pernambuco, Brazil

Freelancer (Remote)

Identification of objects (censored specificity) from a mobile camera for legal purposes.

SUMMARY

Originally from Rio but now based in Recife, I've had the privilege of growing up in two vibrant cities. My passions are as diverse as my background, ranging from an avid love for games and books to an insatiable curiosity for travel and technology. Furthermore, I am always eager to explore new opportunities and challenges that can help me grow both as a professional and as a person, fueled by my passion for learning and applying new technologies to solve real-world problems. I have

been working on Software Development since 2022. Not only that, but I am used to developing Big Data applications that demand high efficiency, scalability, and low cost. All my projects demanded skills in web development, data engineering, CI/CD, Docker, GitHub Actions, and cloud computing, in order to deliver quality solutions to clients.

LANGUAGES

Portuguese Native **English** Proficient German

Beginner

TRAINING / COURSES

The Complete Flutter Development Bootcamp with Dart

Udemy

The Complete 2020 Web Development **Bootcamp**

Udemy

CERTIFICATION

Google Cloud Computing Foundations: Cloud Computing Fundamentals - Locales

Google Cloud Skills Boost

Google Cloud Computing Foundations: Data, ML, and Al in Google Cloud - Locales

Google Cloud Skills Boost

Google Cloud Computing Foundations: Infrastructure in Google Cloud - Locales

Google Cloud Skills Boost

Google Cloud Computing Foundations: Networking

Google Cloud Skills Boost

EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Oncase

A https://www.oncase.com.br

Started as an intern and then worked full-time (Remote)

- Developed Big Data applications with a focus on high efficiency, scalability, and low cost.
- Developed frontend applications using React (JavaScript, TypeScript and HTML/CSS) and Redux.
- Implemented backend functionality using Python frameworks Flask and
- Implemented effective CI/CD pipelines for seamless integration and deployment through Docker and GitHub Actions.
- In general, utilized skills in web development (Django, React and HTML/CSS), data engineering, CI/CD, Docker, GitHub Actions, and cloud
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to achieve project goals.
- Enhanced customer relationships through the delivery of top-notch
- Ensured high-quality and scalable application development.
- Hosted applications on Google Cloud Platform using Cloud Run and Artifact
- Utilized Amazon Web Services for hosting, leveraging services like Amplify, Route53, and Lambda.

Game Developer

Educandus Tecnologia Educacional

Internship (Remote)

 I have worked on web apps (educational simulators) using Construct 3 software and JavaScript mainly.

Gamer Developer

Educandus Tecnologia Educacional

Internship (Remote)

I have worked as a game developer using Construct 3 software and JavaScript, building educational games for students from preschool to high school levels.

Programming Languages

Python	C	C++	JavaScript
TypeScri	pt	Bash	PowerShell
Haskell	Go	Java	Ruby

Web Development

React	Djan	go	Flask	FastAPI
Tailwind CSS		Node.js		JQuery
HTML/CSS		Webpack		

DevOps

CI/CD	Gi	tHub Actions	Docker		
Terraform		Airflow			

Cloud

Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Google Cloud Platform (GCP)

Mobile

React Native	Flutter		
Others			

Git	GitHub	Linux	Databases		
SQL	Postgre	SQL N	longoDB		

Construct 3